Translated by Releska
The sky of the white sea
Let's go and talk
Welcome to my place
Unpreерб pouvoir
Ten years of dream
Very brave
Knowledge is for now
Like snail
It's hard to say
That if you couldn't find it
we could meet for a month
It takes to be happy
You didn't know
I can't let you go
You're always in it
Because you've got to be the smile of the stars
With you, with you, with you
If I were to love you by my hand
With you, I can't let you go
Because you're the one who's different from me
I can't feel anything
I'm going to die!
If you were to test the machine, it would be great!
We were not able to solve this problem!
I don't know where to go...
But I'm not planning to go home.
I can't go home without my family and friends.
I was so happy to be with you together!
Let's do it in the fog!
Ocho-san!
Yes, please!
Thank you!
Let's do it together!
One, two, three, four!
Hm?
Is there really anything you want to do?
Yes!
Ocho-san!
Yes, please!
Thank you!
Let's do it!
What should I do?
Yes, please!
Where are you going?
I'm going to the bathroom!
Yes!
Where did you go?
The sound of the sound!
No!
The sound of the sound is important!
Yes, please!
Where are you going?
I'm going to the bathroom!
No!
Let's go!
What are you doing?
I'm going to the bathroom!
I'm about to open the door!
I don't want to open the door!
You don't need to open the door!
Are you trying to open the door?
I thought you'd open it.
I think I'd open it.
Ah, are you not going to open it?
No, I'm not going to open it.
No, it's not.
Actually, I was able to reach the top of this Tamago.
The top of this Tamago?
No, I was able to reach it before I reached it.
Oh, I thought so. The Tamago of the dream.
The Tamago of the dream?
Yes, I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago.
I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top of this Tamago where I was able to reach the top
There's nothing more.
If you're a star of this island, you can fly and fly.
I see.
Maybe...
Maybe.
If you're a star...
What? What? What? What? What?
I've got something to show you.
What are you doing?
Hey, it's this egg.
What? What is this?
What?
I didn't see anything. It's this egg.
Is this the same egg that was born before?
Huh?
I think so, father.
The color is a little different.
That means it's good.
It's good that the egg is born from this egg.
It's not the same, is it?
This egg?
Is that another egg that looks like this egg?
Is it a egg?
If the egg has been born, that will be revealed.
That's true.
The egg which has a little space.
What are you saying?
Have you ever got inside the egg or your brother?
There isn't that many things I want to show you.
I don't want this egg to be made with food.
I'm not going to lose my mind!
What are you doing?
Everyone, don't you have a good time?
I'm sure that the future generations of the past will be born!
The future generations?
No!
Alright!
This future generations will be born!
I'm sure that the future generations of the past will be born!
Congratulations!
You're a great future generations!
That's right!
That's a good idea for me.
I'm looking forward to seeing you.
You look like Harikichi.
That's right! You look like Harikichi.
That's right. You look like Shitsubusara.
This is how it looks like.
That's how it looks like.
I'll warm you up in the sun.
This is how it looks like.
Of course, it's 24 hours.
That's tough.
That's impossible.
When we go to the toilet,
that's how it looks like.
That's right.
That's how it looks like.
Yeah.
I was thinking of something.
I know that there are a lot of people around here.
But I don't know why I came here.
I don't know why I came here.
Hmm.
Where did you come from?
I came back because I had a father.
Right?
Yeah.
Where did you come from?
I came from here because I had a father.
Yeah.
Even when I was a father,
I had a hard time actually.
That day,
and the shiitake was gone.
I couldn't control the wind.
I can't control the wind.
The wind suddenly turns into the wind.
That's such a bad weather.
The light is too much.
That's right.
What's the point?
Anyway.
It's a time.
I wonder if there's anything I haven't told you yet.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Is that what I'm talking about?
Okay.
Let's go this way.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you, thank you.
What are you doing?
This way!
I've got something really good for you today.
I can't go anywhere without you.
I can't go anywhere with you.
This is...
This is what I'm talking about.
Really?
What?
I heard that there was something that was bad for the first-hand store in Tamago.
But when I look at it, I remember that I had to buy something good for the first-hand store.
What?
That was the first time I saw that.
I wonder who that man is.
Yes, I've been interested in him since then.
I looked for him in the town.
I can't find him.
In the place where Takagaya is walking, there was nothing like that.
It's a strange story, but I don't know where the old lady came from.
That's how I always feel.
Even in this island, even in the whole world.
I'm curious about that old lady.
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka! Kojikuchi-san!
Muka Muka! That old lady is a big girl.
Muka Muka!
Look at this old lady.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
What?
The story of Shenshi and Shanshi,
I think, was a long time ago.
It's true.
I thought that Muka Muka was born from the old lady.
Maybe she's the same girl.
Muka!
Well, that's the story of the old lady.
What's wrong with that?
Did you say that it was the old lady?
Yes, ma'am.
What's wrong with that old lady?
I heard something.
She's always crying.
Do you hear that old lady?
I told her that earlier.
It's all right.
It was like we broke a bridge together.
It was so hard.
And I was able to break a bridge through two dreams.
I thought, because I can break my eggs,
I could tell you that my new year is over.
You can break it through three chains now.
It's impossible to break eggs through three chains.
Shiii!
I was scared, Tashi!
No...
Shiii! I'm so scared!
I'm so scared!
I went to the toilet to put the egg in the toilet and let it go to the toilet after 5 hours!
I was afraid of the blue one!
But I was tired, so I put the egg in the toilet and...
I'll let you go.
I'm tired.
I'm really tired.
I'm so exhausted.
I'm so tired.
I couldn't find the eggs when I was looking for them.
I couldn't find the eggs either.
Then, did you find the eggs that came out?
If I were to find the eggs, I would have found them.
But I couldn't find the eggs that came out last year.
But I found them.
I'm so tired.
Yes, thank you. See you again.
I'm so exhausted.
I really don't want to die.
I wonder if the egg that's gone is the egg that my father bought.
Is this egg that's gone?
Yes, I think it's different.
Yes.
How about this?
Is this a dog?
That's right.
Maybe it's an aliellum.
What are we going to do?
We came to this world where we are going.
What we are going to do is...
We are going to buy a new one.
I think so, right?
If we were to do so, we would have come to the top of the mountain.
Yeah.
The mountain that was born from that mountain...
...is a promise.
Yeah.
Then, the mountain that was born...
The mountain that was born from that mountain...
Let's see.
Yeah.
What's going on?
Let's go over here.
There it is.
Over there.
Yeah.
I don't think there will be such a power in the mountain.
Yeah, right?
Yeah.
Is it okay?
It's hard. It's hard.
Dad, what happened to you?
That mountain was lost.
That mountain?
Yeah.
Let's go.
What's going on?
It's like a dream.
There's a lot of wind, but we can't find it.
Even if the mountain is looking for it, it's a change.
What's going on?
The mountain that was born from that mountain was a lot of wind.
It's a secret.
What?
If you eat eggs, you'll get a stomachache.
Hmm, but where did you go?
Did you get a stomachache?
No, I didn't do that.
I told you to eat a big egg with a cat panda.
Tell me!
Who brought it?
The egg is gone.
Hey, the egg is gone.
I'm afraid.
It's a big egg.
Hey, it's a big egg.
I'm afraid.
I can't even eat this egg.
You're so cute, aren't you?
If you eat it before the eyes, I'll eat a big egg.
I'm afraid.
A big egg won't stop eating.
What are you doing?
You're doing the same job as me.
I'm afraid.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I want you to eat a big egg.
No, no.
You don't have to say anything stupid.
Hurry up and do your homework!
No!
Run!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What's wrong, you!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I'm going to get back to you.
Stop!
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm going to get back to you!
Stop!
Please!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
I can't tolerate anyone in today's class anymore.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Stop!
Oh, no!
Stop it!
Are you okay, Lancaster?
Hurry up and meet me!
Yes!
I'm thinking of you.
Oh, no!
What are you doing?
It's not like the egg is gone!
Hurry up and meet me!
Oh, no!
I'm thinking of you!
I'm tired of my legs!
I'm a human!
What's going on?
Now, I'm going to make the egg.
Huh?
Wow!
It's really good!
I'm going to make a big egg.
Oh, no!
Huh?
It's too long of a lot!
Really!
Good job!
Hmm!
Oh, no!
May we make it?
Get right away, everyone.
Faces to move forward.
Yes!
Aiya!
Oh!
Please stop!
Here you go!
Huh?
Here.
Big brother.
Now that you're here, I can't wait to see you again.
Mr. Hikata...
The two of them are cute, so they're cute, right?
Let's go together!
Yeah!
It's been a long time since I've been here.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Oh, Tenba.
I didn't expect you to be here today.
But I know what you're thinking.
I've been waiting for you since I started to become your friend.
I see.
I've been waiting for you for a long time to protect me.
I've been waiting for you since I started to become your friend.
When I'm going to be your friend, I'll be your friend.
I'll stay home I've been waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you, so I'll be around you.
I'll be here, so I'll be around you.
I'll be around you.
I will be there for you.
Just to be happy, I'll be there for you.
just to be happy, I'll be there for you.
Eh, time machine's running out?
Are you sure that you're really gonna do it?
I did it!
I did it.
You're really gonna do it.
But I think you guys will do the same thing.
Uwaaaah!
What?
Why did you turn around?
I can't see anything, I can't hear anything!
Mugamuka! Where are you?
Next time on Mugamuka Paradais,
Mugamuka on the Yamiko Zone,
I'll be looking forward to Mugamuka!
Uwaaah!